politicsandwar.com 2019-11-18

# Politics & War - Rule your own country!

Privacy Policy

### Politics and War Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy describes how your personal information is collected, used, and shared when you visit or make a purchase from https://politicsandwar.com (the "Game"), related sub-domains such as http://test.politicsandwar.com (also the "Game"), as well as the official Politics and War Google Play Store applications for Android devices also (the "Game"). 

SECTION 1: PERSONAL INFORMATION WE COLLECT

When you visit the Game, we automatically collect certain information about your device, including information about your web browser, IP address, time zone, and some of the cookies that are installed on your device. Additionally, as you use the Game, we collect information about the individual web pages or products that you view, what websites or search terms referred you to the Game, and information about how you interact with the Game. We refer to this automatically-collected information as “Device Information.” 

We collect Device Information using the following technologies: 

\- “Cookies” are data files that are placed on your device or computer and often include an anonymous unique identifier. For more information about cookies, and how to disable cookies, visit http://www.allaboutcookies.org. 

\- “Log files” track actions occurring on the Game, and collect data including your IP address, browser type, Internet service provider, referring/exit pages, and date/time stamps. 

\- “Web beacons,” “tags,” and “pixels” are electronic files used to record information about how you use the Game. 

Additionally when you make a purchase or attempt to make a purchase through the Game, we collect certain information from you, including your name, email address, and PayPal account information. We refer to this information as “Order Information.” All Credit Card, bank, and other financial information is stored and processed by PayPal, and the Game does not have access to or otherwise store this information. 

Users of the Game have the option to become "Verified" in the Game. This process, known as "Verification", is completely optional, and is never required to play the Game. The Verification process requires sending a personal photograph of the user via email to the Game, which is stored on an offline server. This information, including photographs, are used only to ensure that a single person is not operating multiple accounts. This Verification information is never made public, will never be sold, and should the Game ever be sold at a future date, all Verification information will be destroyed. Verification information is not kept after a user quits the Game or deletes their Game account. 

When we talk about “Personal Information” in this Privacy Policy, we are talking about all kinds of information outlined in SECTION 1. 

SECTION 2: HOW DO WE USE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?

We use the Order Information that we collect generally to fulfill any orders placed through the Game (including arranging for issuance of digital goods and providing you with invoices and/or order confirmations). Additionally, we use this Order Information to: 

Communicate with you; Screen our orders for potential risk or fraud; and when in line with the preferences you have shared with us, provide you with information or advertising relating to our products or services. 

We use the Device Information that we collect to help us screen for potential risk and fraud (in particular, your IP address), and more generally to improve and optimize the Game (for example, by generating analytics about how our customers browse and interact with the Game, and to assess the success of our marketing and advertising campaigns). 

SECTION 3: SHARING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

We do not and will never share your information with third parties. 

We use Google Analytics to help us understand how our customers use the Game--you can read more about how Google uses your Personal Information here: https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/. You can also opt-out of Google Analytics here: https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout. 

We use Google Adsense to help us generate revenue to pay for the Game and offer it as a free-to-play service for all--you can read more about how Google uses your Personal Information here: https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/. You can also opt-out of Google Adsense here: https://www.google.com/settings/ads/anonymous. 

Finally, we may also share your Personal Information to comply with applicable laws and regulations, to respond to a subpoena, search warrant or other lawful request for information we receive, or to otherwise protect our rights. 

SECTION 4: BEHAVIORAL ADVERTISING

As described above, Google may use your Personal Information to provide you with targeted advertisements or marketing communications we believe may be of interest to you. For more information about how targeted advertising works, you can visit the Network Advertising Initiative’s (“NAI”) educational page at http://www.networkadvertising.org/understanding-online-advertising/how-does-it-work. 

You can opt out of Google's targeted advertising here: https://www.google.com/settings/ads/anonymous 

Additionally, you can opt out of some of these services by visiting the Digital Advertising Alliance’s opt-out portal at: http://optout.aboutads.info/. 

SECTION 5: DO NOT TRACK

Please note that we do not alter our Game's data collection and use practices when we see a Do Not Track signal from your browser. 

SECTION 6: YOUR RIGHTS

If you are a European resident, you have the right to access personal information we hold about you and to ask that your personal information be corrected, updated, or deleted. If you would like to exercise this right, please contact us through the contact information below. 

Additionally, if you are a European resident we note that we are processing your information in order to fulfill contracts we might have with you (for example if you make an order through the Game), or otherwise to pursue our legitimate business interests listed above. Additionally, please note that your information will be transferred outside of Europe, including to the United States. 

SECTION 7: DATA RETENTION

When you place an order through the Game, we will maintain your Order Information for our records unless and until you ask us to delete this information. This does not include any sensitive financial information, such as Credit Card or Bank information, which we never store. 

SECTION 8: MINORS

The Game is not intended for individuals under the age of 13. 

8.1: COPPA (Children Online Privacy Protection Act) 

When it comes to the collection of personal information from children under 13, the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) puts parents in control. The Federal Trade Commission, the nation's consumer protection agency, enforces the COPPA Rule, which spells out what operators of websites and online services must do to protect children's privacy and safety online. 

We do not specifically market to children under 13, and per our Terms and Conditions, children under 13 years of age are not allowed to play the Game, and all users must specifically agree that they are 13 years of age or older before being able to play the Game. 

SECTION 9: CALIFORNIA ONLINE PRIVACY PROTECTION ACT (CalOPPA)

CalOPPA is the first state law in the nation to require commercial websites and online services to post a privacy policy. The law's reach stretches well beyond California to require a person or company in the United States (and conceivably the world) that operates websites collecting personally identifiable information from California consumers to post a conspicuous privacy policy on its website stating exactly the information being collected and those individuals with whom it is being shared, and to comply with this policy. See more at: <http://consumercal.org/california-online-privacy-protection-act-caloppa/#sthash.0FdRbT51.dpuf>

9.1: According to CalOPPA we agree to the following:

\- Users can visit our site anonymously.

\- Once this privacy policy is created, we will add a link to it on our home page or as a minimum on the first significant page after entering our website.

\- Our Privacy Policy link includes the word 'Privacy' and can be easily be found on the page specified above.

9.2: Does our site allow third-party behavioral tracking?

It's also important to note that we allow third-party behavioral tracking. For more information, see SECTION 3.

SECTION 10: FAIR INFORMATION PRACTICES

The Fair Information Practices Principles form the backbone of privacy law in the United States and the concepts they include have played a significant role in the development of data protection laws around the globe. Understanding the Fair Information Practice Principles and how they should be implemented is critical to comply with the various privacy laws that protect personal information. 

10.1: In order to be in line with Fair Information Practices we will take the following responsive action, should a data breach occur:

We will notify the users via email within 30 business days

We will notify the users via in-site notification within 30 business days

SECTION 11: CAN SPAM ACT

The CAN-SPAM Act is a law that sets the rules for commercial email, establishes requirements for commercial messages, gives recipients the right to have emails stopped from being sent to them, and spells out tough penalties for violations. 

10.1: We collect your email address in order to:

\- Send information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions.

10.2: To be in accordance with CAN-SPAM we agree to the following:

\- NOT use false or misleading subjects or email addresses.

\- Identify the message as an advertisement in some reasonable way.

\- Include the physical address of our business or site headquarters.

\- Monitor third-party email marketing services for compliance, if one is used.

\- Honor opt-out/unsubscribe requests quickly.

\- Follow the instructions at the bottom of each email.

If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, you can email us at politicsandwaronline@gmail.com and we will promptly remove you from ALL correspondence. 

SECTION 11: CHANGES

We may update this privacy policy from time to time in order to reflect, for example, changes to our practices or for other operational, legal or regulatory reasons. 

This Privacy Policy was last updated on May 22, 2018, and was amended in accordance with the General Data Protection Regulations law in the European Union. 

SECTION 12: CONTACT US

For more information about our privacy practices, if you have questions, or if you would like to make a complaint, please contact us by e-mail at privacy@politicsandwar.com.
